Contact

denatiles@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dena-iles-7aa313100 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Business Development Territory Management Customer Retention

Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

ACLS

BLS

Honors-Awards

Life Saver Award

Dena Iles

Critical Care Clinical Educator RN, BSN, CCRN Daphne

Summary

Experience as a Registered Nurse, Critical Care Educator and Outside Sales Representative. Skilled in Customer Service, Business Development, Cold Calling, Critical Thinking, and Customer Retention. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from University of Alabama.

Experience

Baptist Health Care Critical Care Clinical Educator November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months) Pensacola, Florida

James H Faulkner State Community College Nursing Adjuct Clinical Instructor June 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 7 months) Bay Minette, Alabama

Thomas Hospital Registered Nurse SICU November 2013 - November 2018 (5 years 1 month) United States, Fairhope, AI

Cardinal Health
Pharmacy Business Consultant
September 2004 - May 2008 (3 years 9 months)
United States

Air Science of Alabama
Outside Sales Representative
July 2000 - July 2004 (4 years 1 month)
United States

W&O Supply Inside Sales July 1998 - July 2000 (2 years 1 month) United States

AmSouth Bank Bank Teller July 1995 - July 1999 (4 years 1 month) United States

Education

University of Alabama

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2016 - 2017)

James H Faulkner State Community College Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2013)